export const cityFactList = [{
   prompt: "Learn about Washington State...",
   answer: "Are you ready??? Click the 'Next' and 'Back' buttons to navigate through the slide deck"
}, {
   prompt: "What is Washington's state bird?",
   answer: "American Goldfinch - The American Goldfinch is characerized by it's black cap and black wings, and it's song is long, high, and sweet",
   difficulty: "m",
   img: "/"
}, {
   prompt: "What is Washington's state insect?",
   answer: "Green Darner Dragonfly - This bug has a relatively short life of just one summer, however, it spends one to five years as an underwater larva or nymph",
   difficulty: "m",
   img: "/"
}, {
   prompt: "What is Washington's official waterfall?",
   answer: "Palouse Falls",
   difficulty: "h",
   img: "/"
}, {
   prompt: "Which state operates the largest ferry fleet in the United States?",
   answer: "Washington states does and is second globally. In total there are 21 ferries.",
   difficulty: "e",
   img: "/"
}, {
   prompt: "Ever wonder what state grows the most apples??",
   answer: "Well look no further because Washington state has you covered with all your apple needs",
   difficulty: "e",
   img: "/"
}, {
   prompt: "Thirsty for some wine?? Of course you have to be over the age of 21. Sorry kiddos looks like your stuck drinking apple juice.",
   answer: "Well Washington is the second-largest wine-producing region in the US",
   difficulty: "e",
   img: "/"
}, {
   prompt: "How many federally recognized Native tribes reside in Washington State?",
   answer: "29",
   difficulty: "h",
   img: "/"
}, {
   prompt: "What is the tallest mountain in Washington?",
   answer: "Mount Rainier",
   difficulty: "h",
   img: "/"
}, {
   prompt: "How many named glaciers are in Washington?",
   answer: "186",
   difficulty: "h",
   img: "/"
}, {
   prompt: "How many national parks does Washington have?",
   answer: "3",
   difficulty: "m",
   img: "/"
}, {
   prompt: "What famous companies were founded in Washington state?",
   answer: "Boeing, Amazon, Starbucks, those are just some of the few big ones",
   difficulty: "m",
   img: "/"
}, {
   prompt: "What fictional novel written by Stephanie Meyer took place in Washington state?",
   answer: "Twilight!!",
   difficulty: "e",
   img: "/"
}]